Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Trade Divisions and Conferences records 1942-2003 IBT0013
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Trade Divisions and Conferences records
1942-2003
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
IBT0013
22.5 Linear Feet
This collections contains the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Trade Division and Conference records dating from 1942-2003.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Scope and Contents
This collections contains the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Trade Division and Conference records dating from 1942-2003.
Arrangement
Organized into four series: Public Service Diviion, Airline Division, Bakery Conderence Proceedings and Natinoal Warehouse Division.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, [2012] [2012.008, 2012.009, 2012.023, 2012.024].
Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Conferences; Labor; Labor unions
- Public Services Division, 1993-2003; Series 1; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Conference Materials, 1993-2003; Series 1 Subseries 1; 0.5 Linear Feet
    - A Compendium of State Public sector Labor Relations Laws, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Ohio Conference of Teamsters Meeting, 1993 August 25; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - A Compendium of State Public sector Labor Relations; Errata Sheet, 1994 March; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Contract Costing, 1995 November 14; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Public Employee Division conference Survey, 1995 May 1-4; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Public Employee Trade Division Conference, 2000 May 8-11; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Public Employee Annual Conference, 2001 May 1-4; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Public Employee Annual Conference; Transparencies, 2001 May 1-4; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Public Service Division Annual Conference, 2003 April 28 - May 1; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Pamphlet: Why Are Thousands Of Public Employees Joining The Teamsters Union?, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Airline Division, 1947-2002; Series 2; 18.5 Linear Feet
  Organized in to four subseries: Legal Files, Publications, Manuals and Promotional material.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the records of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Airline Division dating from 1947-2002. Materials include legal files, publications, manuals and promotional material.
  - Legal Files, Series 2 Subseries 1
    - Saturn/TIA Merger, 1974 - 1977; Series 2 Suberies 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Delta/Northwest Merger, June 1997- August 1997; Series 2 Suberies 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - American v APFA, 1987-1988; Series 2 Suberies 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Seniority Integration of Continental and frontier Pilots, 29 May 1987; Series 2 Suberies 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Integration of PanAm and National Seniority lists, 30 January 1981; Series 2 Suberies 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Northcentral/Southern merger of the F.A. Seniority list, 28 June 1979; Series 2 Suberies 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - UAL/Capital Arbitration, 5 July 1961; Series 2 Suberies 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Aerican/APFA Arbitration, July 1987; Series 2 Suberies 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Cal/Txi F.A. Seniority Integration, May 1984; Series 2 Suberies 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Western/Continental Merger, 1979; Series 2 Suberies 1 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Republic/Airwest Seniority Integration Dispute (1/4), 21 June 1982; Series 2 Suberies 1 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Republic/Airwest Seniority Integration Dispute (2/4), 21 June 1982; Series 2 Suberies 1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Republic/Airwest Seniority Integration Dispute (3/4), 21 June 1982; Series 2 Suberies 1 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Republic/Airwest Seniority Integration Dispute (4/4), 21 June 1982; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - PanAm/ National F.A. Integration, 30 January 1981; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - United/PanAm, September 1986; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Agreement - Piedmont Aviators Inc. and Flight Attendents, 5 Februar 1986; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Agreement - Western Airlines and Continental Airlines, Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Constitution and Bylaws of the Association fo Flight Attendents, 1973-1985; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Merger Policies and Related Employee Protective Provision, Janaury 1985; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Series 2 Subseries 2
    - Miscellaneous Correspondences in the IBT Airline Division, 1991-1997; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Misc Newsletters (1/3), 1991-1992; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Misc Newsletters (2/3), April - August 1992; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Misc Newsletters (3/3), 1992 - 1993; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Newsletters [1/2], 1997-2001; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Newsletters [2/2], 2002-2008 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - 2000 Times, 1997 - 1998; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Common Ground, 1998 - 2002; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Teamsters Airline Journal, January-Spring 2003; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Teamsters Airline Journal, Spring-Fall 2007; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Teamsters Airline Journal, 2004 - 2006; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - The Teamster Leader, 2006 - 2008; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - CAL Fleet Service Teamsters News, June-December 2009; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - CAL Fleet Service Teamsters News, January-December 2010; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Agreement between IBT and CWA Airline Customer Service Employees Association and U.S. Airways and America West Airlines, INC., December 2005; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - General Files: Memos, miscellaneous reports, 1959-1964; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - General Files: Memos and Reports on Local 19, 1959-1970; Series Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Airline Division Files Master Documents, 1996-2005 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Summary and Comparison of Health and Welfare Plans, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Teamsters Miscellaneous Security Trust Fund, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Summary of Flight Attendant Wages, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Central States Conference World Airlines Health and Welfare Proposal, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Teamsters Airlines Journals, 2004-2007 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Airlines Division Shop Steward Manual, Undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Local 2000 Flyer, Undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Our Time, Who Controls What It's Worth booklet, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Local 2707 Newsletter, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Eight Times Newsletter, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Skyword Newsletter, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Report at the 19th Convention, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Flightlog Magazine, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Employee Benefit Insurance Plan, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Manuals, undated; Series 2 Subseries 3
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Index, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Organizing Outline, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual NMB-NRLB Cards, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual NLRB Rules, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual NLRB Structures, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual NMB rules, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual RWY. Labor Act, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Case NO R-1706, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual NMB-3, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Official Ballot, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Federal Mediators, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Airline-Union, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Application for Mediation Services, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Contracts, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Negotiations, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Strike Sanction Forms, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Strike Info, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Union Security Clauses, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Grievance Form, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual IAM-IBT Election, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Survey Forms, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Section II Header, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Area Confrences, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Vice Presidents, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual General Organizers, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Policy committee, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Airline Locals, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Section 3 Header, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual U.S. Air Carriers, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual City Airport Codes, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual US Airports, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Functions of C.A.B., Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Section IV Header, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Local Structures, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Armed SVCS Committee, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Employee Outlook, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Facts & Figures, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Airline Division - Organizing Manual Air Route Maps, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Shop Steward Manual, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Accident, Incident, and Drug testing manuals, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - By-Laws of Teamsters, Airline, Areospace & Allied Employees, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Promotional material, 2002-2004; Series 2 Subseries 4
    - Pamphlets and Advertisments, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Pamphlets and Advertisments [2], 2010; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Calenders, Postcards, & Stickers, 2002-2004; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Company Files, 1990s - 2000s; Series 2 Subseries 5; 17 Linear Feet
    This subseries contains IBT airline division materials related to specific airlines and air cargo companies dating from the 1990s and 2000s.
    Airlines and companies included are Air Transport International, Air Tran Airways, Bonk Air Transportation, Centurion Air Cargo, Challenge Air Cargo, Chautauqua Air, Comair/Delta Airlines, EG & G Technical Services, Executive Jet Aviation, ExpressJet, Frontier Airlines, Gemini Air Cargo, Go Jet Airlines, Grand Aire Express, Great Lakes Aviation, Kalitta Air, Mid-Atlantic Airways, NetJets, North American Airlines, Northwest Airlines, Piedmont/Allegheny Airlines, Pinnacle Air, PSA Airlines, Republic Airways, Swissport USA, Transmeridian Airlines, Trans States Airlines, U.S. Airways, World Airways, and Zantop International.
    Specific materials include correspondence, memoranda, contracts/negotiation, financial information, newsletters, news clippings, seniority lists, National Mediation Board materials, health/welfare information, union election ballots, union representation applications, Central States Pension Fund materials, grievances, FAQs, handbooks/manuals, flyers, and other miscellaneous items.
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by airline/company name. Materials for each company have yet to be further organized.
    General
    The records in this subseries are scheduled to be reviewed in 2017.
    - Air Transportation International, 2000s; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 11)
      Air Transportation International: correspondence, contracts/negotiation, health/welfare/disability information, meeting notes, seniority lists, financial information, and news clippings.
    - Air Transportation International, 2000s; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 12)
      Air Transportation International: correspondence, contracts, handbooks, health/welfare information, and financial information.
    - Air Transportation International - Centurion Air Cargo, 2000s; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 13)
      Air Transportation International: correspondence, contracts, news clippings, and financial information.
      Air Tran Airways: correspondence, memoranda, and legal proceedings.
      Bonk Air Transporation: National Mediation Board materials.
      Centurion Air Cargo: contracts/negotiation.
    - Centurion Air Cargo, 2000s; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 14)
      Centurion Air Cargo: contracts/negotiation, correspondence, news clippings, and meeting notes.
    - Centurion Air Cargo - Comair/Delta Airlines, 2000s; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 15)
      Centurion Air Cargo: contracts.
      Challenge Air Cargo: contracts.
      Chautauqua Airlines: correspondence, financial information, and legal proceedings.
      Comair/Delta Airlines: correspondence, meeting mintues, contracts/negotiation, financial information, company information, staffing, and legal proceedings.
    - Comair/Delta Airlines, 2000s; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 16)
      Comair/Delta Airlines: correspondence, memoranda, newsletters, news clippings, seniority lists, contracts/negotiation, and legal proceedings.
    - Comair/Delta Airlines - Great Lakes Aviation, 2000s; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 17)
      Comair/Delta Airlines: correspondence, news clippings, seniority lists, financial information, employee information, and legal proceedings.
      EG + G Technical Services: contracts and company policies.
      Executive Jet Aviation: correspondence, contracts/negotiation, National Mediation Board materials, and union representation applications.
      ExpressJet Airlines: National Mediation Board materials.
      Frontier Airlines: National Mediation Board materials.
      Gemini Air Cargo: contracts and seniority lists.
      GoJet Airlines: correspondence and National Mediation Board materials.
      Grand Aire Express: contracts.
      Great Lakes Aviation: correspondence, contracts, payrolll information, handbooks/manuals, health/welfare information, and National Mediation Board materials.
    - Great Lakes Aviation - Piedmont/Allegheny Airlines, 2000s; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 18)
      Great Lakes Aviation: correspondence, contracts, training manuals, flyers, news clippings, and union representation applications.
      Kalitta Air: correspondence and National Mediation Board materials.
      Mid-Atlantic Airways: correspondence and FAQs.
      Net Jets: correspondence and union election ballots.
      North American Airlines: correspondence, newsletters, FAQs, and National Mediation Board materials.
      Northwest Airlines: FAQs, flyers, company information, and union information.
      Piedmont/Allegheny Airlines: correspondence, contracts, grievances, National Mediation Board materials, and union representation applications.
    - Piedmont/Allegheny Airlines - U.S. Airways, 2000s; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 19)
      Piedmont/Allegheny Airlines: correspondence, contracts, health/welfare information, company information, and National Mediation Board materials.
      Pinnacle Air: contracts.
      PSA Airlines: correspondence, contracts, company information, DRIVE materials, and National Mediation Board materials.
      Republic Airways: contracts.
      Swissport USA: correspondence and National Mediation Board materials.
      Tradewinds Airlines: legal correspondence.
      TransMeridian Airlines: correspondence.
      Trans States Airlines: contracts.
      U.S. Airways: correspondence, contracts, seniority lists, union handbooks, health/welfare information, company information, and National Mediation Board materials.
    - U.S. Airways - World Airways, 2000s; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 20)
      U.S. Airways: correspondence, contracts, newsletters, seniority lists, news clippings, earning reports, and National Mediation Board materials.
      World Airways: correspondence, contracts/negotiation, Central States Pension Fund materials, seniority lists, health/welfare information, grievances, news clippings, and union election ballots.
    - World Airways, 1990s - 2000s; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 21)
      World Airways: contracts/negotiation and financial information.
    - World Airways - Zantop International, 2000s; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 22)
      World Airways: correspondence, contracts/negotiation, company information, financial information, Central States Pension Fund materials, newsletters, and news clippings.
      Zantop International: correspondence.
  - Subject Files, 1980-2008; Series 2 Subseries 6; 2.5 Linear Feet
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically.
    This subseries contains subject files related to the Teamsters Airline Division dating from 1980-2008. Included are Airline Division budget, training, health and welfare, arbitration and grievance materials, as well as materials from various aviation and flight attendant unions, Teamsters local unions, the National Mediation Board, the Federal Aviation Administration, and the Transportation Security Administration.
    - Aircraft Services International Group, 2000-2004; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Arbitration [1/2], 1982-2000; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Arbitration [2/2], 1980-1990; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Association of Flight Attendants, 2000-2005; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - "Aviation Daily" Newsletter, 2005-2008; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Aviation Maintenance Fraternal Association, 2003-2004; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Bargaining Training, 1996; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Coalition of Flight Attendant Unions, 2000-2001; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Criminal History Records Checks, 2001-2002; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Federal Aviation Administration, 1998-2005; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Flight Attendent Certification [1/2], 2003; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Flight Attendant Certification [2/2], 2002-2004; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Flight Attendant Training [1/2], 1999-2004; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Flight Attendant Training [2/2], 2003-2004; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Grievances, 2003-2006; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Health and Welfare Benefits [1/2], 2000-2008; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Health and Welfare Benefits [2/2], 1996-2008; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - IBT Local 513, 2003-2008; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - IBT Local 747, 2004; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Master Grievance Policy Forms, 2004; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - National Mediation Board, 2004-2007; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Pay Information, 2004-2006; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Professional Standards Committee, 2005-2008; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Professional Standards Training [1/2], 2008; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Professional Standards Training [2/2], 2008; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Stewards Seminars [1/2], 2003; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Stewards Seminars [2/2], 2006; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Stewards Workshop, 2006; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Teamsters Airline Division Budget [1/2], 2000; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Teamsters Airline Division Budget [2/2], 2001-2002; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Teamsters Airline Division: General [1/2], 2004-2008; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Teamsters Airline Divison: General [2/2], 2006-2007; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Teamsters Airline Division Office Closure, 2007; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Teamsters Airline Division Restructuring, 2004-2008; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Teamsters DRIVE [1/2], 2004; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Teamsters DRIVE [2/2], 2004-2007; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Teamsters Training and Development [1/2], 2007; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Teamsters Training and Development [2/2], 2007-2008; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Transport Workers Union, 1999-2004; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Transportation Security Administration, 2004; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Union Dues, 2002-2005; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Airline Division Pin, ND, IBT0013 Series 2 (Box Shared Box 34, Folder 8)
- Bakery Conference Proceedings, 1942-1973; Series 3; 1 Linear Feet
  Arranged chronologically
  The materials in this series include the transcripts of proceedings of the Teamsters National Bakery Conference. The dates range from 1942-1973. There are some gaps between the years where no transcript of proceedings exists.
  - Proceedings, 1942 February 20-21; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Proceedings, 1944 May 1-3; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Proceedings, 1946 June 24-26; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Proceedings, 1953 February 19-21; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Proceedings, 1955 September 12-14; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Proceedings, 1958 September 17-19; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Proceedings, 1959 August 12-14; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Proceedings, 1961 September 18-20; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Proceedings, 1962 August 20-22; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Proceedings, 1963 August 12-14; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Proceedings, 1964 August 10-12; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Proceedings, 1965 August 16-19; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Proceedings, 1966 August 17-19; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 4)